[
  {
    "title": "State Abbrevations",
    "id": 0,
    "cards": [
      {
        "id": 0,
        "prompt": "Arizona",
        "answer": "AR"
      },
      {
        "id": 1,
        "prompt": "California",
        "answer": "CA"
      },
      {
        "id": 2,
        "prompt": "Huawai",
        "answer": "HI"
      },
      {
        "id": 3,
        "prompt": "Kansas",
        "answer": "KS"
      },
      {
        "id": 4,
        "prompt": "Texas",
        "answer": "TX"
      },
      {
        "id": 5,
        "prompt": "Maryland",
        "answer": "MD"
      },
      {
        "id": 6,
        "prompt": "New york",
        "answer": "NY"
      },
      {
        "id": 7,
        "prompt": "WashingTon",
        "answer": "WA"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "title": "State Capitals",
    "id": 1,
    "cards": [
      {
        "id": 0,
        "prompt": "Arizona",
        "answer": "AR"
      },
      {
        "id": 1,
        "prompt": "California",
        "answer": "CA"
      },
      {
        "id": 2,
        "prompt": "Huawai",
        "answer": "HI"
      },
      {
        "id": 3,
        "prompt": "Kansas",
        "answer": "KS"
      },
      {
        "id": 4,
        "prompt": "Texas",
        "answer": "TX"
      },
      {
        "id": 5,
        "prompt": "Maryland",
        "answer": "MD"
      },
      {
        "id": 6,
        "prompt": "New york",
        "answer": "NY"
      },
      {
        "id": 7,
        "prompt": "WashingTon",
        "answer": "WA"
      }
    ]
  }
]
